Get exactly what you want.
Babygirl is a romance, thriller film directed by Halina Reijn.
A high-powered CEO puts her career and family on the line when she
begins a torrid affair with her much younger intern.
Romy, played by Nicole Kidman.
Samuel, played by Harris Dickinson.
Jacob, played by Antonio Banderas.
Isabel, played by Esther-Rose McGregor.
Esme, played by Sophie Wilde.
Nora, played by Vaughan Reilly.
Babygirl is a 2024 American erotic thriller film written,
directed, and produced by Halina Reijn.
The film stars Nicole Kidman as a high-powered CEO who puts her career and family on the
line when she begins an affair with a much younger intern (Harris Dickinson).
Sophie Wilde and Antonio Banderas also star.
Babygirl premiered at the 81st Venice International Film Festival on August 30, 2024, where Kidman won the Volpi Cup for Best Actress, followed by a
premiere at the 2024 Toronto International Film Festival on September 10, 2024, with a wide theatrical release by A24 on December 25, 2024.
It received positive reviews and became a box office success,
grossing $64.7 million on a $20 million budget.
It was named one of the top ten films of 2024 by the National Board of
Review, where Kidman was also awarded the Best Actress prize.
The film explores themes of infidelity, new york city, husband
wife relationship, sexual frustration, sexuality.
The tone is emotional and intense.